Hello everyone, I'm Sherry from Mindless Designer.
Today is our last live stream from a year ago.
The theme of this live stream is Mindless Designer Study Day.
This is the production process of this set of clothes by my mother-in-law Hannah.
It will include some of her accessories.
For example, a pair of jeans, a scarf, a bag, and some socks.
Let's get started.
First of all, the process is the same as before.
We need to make a limited edition.
Then we need to change the proportion.
Here we need to pay attention to the model's shoulder.
We need to align the shoulder line as much as possible.
It's best to have a double-layer photo frame, including her waist.
Then click OK.
After we have the background picture,
we can use the internal photo frame.
We can use a multi-layer tool to draw a line along the curve of the clothes.
After the drawing process, press the Ctrl key to create a curve point.
My voice is a little hoarse today.
I'm sorry.
After creating a pattern,
I will draw the inner line in the middle of it.
Then we can skip the drawing process.
Then we can arrange the pattern.
In the process of arranging,
considering that the shirt is on one side and outside the other side,
I will pull the pattern out a little bit.
After arranging,
I see that the sleeves can't wrap the model very well.
So I will manually use our Gizmo.
Gizmo is...
Oh, I can't remember what it's called in Chinese.
It's a positioning tool.
Rotate it and let it go for a while.
Then we will sew it.
Use the sewing tool to sew the sleeves and the top of the shirt together.
Then sew the middle of the back as well.
After sewing, I sometimes sew the inner line in 3D.
It's more convenient.
Let me drink some water.
I think my voice is too hoarse.
After creating a pattern, I found that
I forgot to sew the sleeves on both sides.
So everyone usually forgets
to check the sewing line before opening the pattern.
Is there any problem with your sewing line?
Is there any seam missing?
Because sometimes,
like the sleeves here,
it's not very serious.
Other places may affect the effect of your dress.
Then I will make some adjustments to her collar.
Because I want to add another collar to her top.
So this,
here,
this little one,
actually we call it a collar,
I will make it shorter.
Then,
I think this shirt looks a little too loose.
So I will choose to add a dot on the side of it.
This can make it a waist-hugging shirt.
After I finished the dot,
you can see that her waist will be closed here.
Then add the position of the side dot,
the best position is
the thinnest position of the model's waist.
After adding it,
I will probably make some adjustments to it.
For example,
I will change this straight line point to a curve line point.
Then the side will be a more smooth curve line.
Then,
here,
you can see that
our bottom is not flat.
It's a little bit curved like this.
Actually,
the main reason is because
on the side of our model,
there is a corner.
Look,
there is also a corner here.
Adding this line is a straight line,
so there will be a problem like this,
which is not very flat.
So,
we need to add a few curve points to it.
Then,
one,
we want it to be a straight corner on the side here.
So that,
when the top and the bottom of our model are parallel,
it will be flat here.
Then,
we will add a few curve points.
Because our model,
the girl's shirt is usually
on the right side,
but not on the left side.
So,
your curve point is actually on the left side,
because you have to wear it through the curve point.
After that,
I will use the button button tool,
to remember the button button and the button button.
Then,
I will go to the object window of the property editor,
and adjust these,
including its width,
and so on.
After adjusting,
I will freeze all the panels,
and then draw a vertical panel.
Of course,
I don't have reference pictures here.
I just draw it
based on my own feeling.
Then,
I will use the edit curve tool
to adjust it a little bit.
Also,
adjust the length of the back center.
Then,
sew them up.
After sewing them up,
it is also to arrange
on this arrangement point at the neck.
After arranging,
I will use the inner line to draw a line.
After drawing this line,
I will use the folding tool
to turn the collar down along this inner line.
After turning it down,
you can see our collar.
Because here,
I open the single display,
so our collar,
it is black.
It has a black side.
In fact,
this means that
this panel
is facing the back side.
The collar is facing the back side.
Here,
this is the single display.
OK.
Then,
I will activate the panel
and let it model.
After modeling,
I want to say that
I want to make a buckle for it.
So,
I draw a rectangular panel.
OK.
After the panel is done,
I will create the sewing line.
After that,
I will add it to the side.
In this way,
this rectangular panel
will be added to the side automatically.
OK.
Then,
I will choose these clothing panels.
I will use a shrink.
After using the shrink,
you can see that
the whole clothing
will be more close to the collar.
It will be close to our collar.
Then,
I will freeze it first.
Because we are going to do the outer clothing,
the outer layer.
OK.
After that,
I will make a belt for it.
Because I want to make
the skirt for it.
OK.
After making the belt,
I will draw some rectangles first.
Then,
I will sew the sides.
OK.
If you have any questions,
you can ask me in the comments.
How to sew.
OK.
Here I have to explain why I have to copy 3 pieces of the pattern.
Because I am going to make the skirt for the next step.
The waistband here is normal length.
For the skirt pattern, because in the end this skirt pattern
If you want to make a white skirt, or if you want to make a dress skirt,
The pattern like this will be turned inside out.
This pattern will be folded inside out.
So if you want to make a skirt that is equal to the waistband,
You have to make 3 of them exactly the same, and then combine them together.
This way, the length after it is folded will be the same as the waistband.
And then also combine the sides of these two patterns.
And then remove the excess points on top.
And then I will redo this pattern.
Redo its 2D position separately.
And then we are going to draw the inner lines that are used to fold.
Yes, it is not easy to transform a skirt.
Then select the edges on both sides.
Here we have to select the inner line created by the curve.
After selecting this function, you can see that some inner lines will be automatically generated.
And then there is an expanded number here.
You can think about why I chose the number 14.
Then I will answer it by myself.
Because the reason is that if you expand, if you want to,
Because these patterns are folded into a group of three lines, right?
Because we just have three sets of patterns.
Then are we going to divide the pattern into three multiple sections?
For example, we are going to divide it into 15 sections.
Is there 14 lines in the middle?
Is it three times minus one?
So when you are drawing the inner line of this white circle,
Be sure to remember to select the inner line generated by the curve.
Here is three times minus one.
If you can't follow it now, it doesn't matter.
Because there will be our recording later.
And then this time, the whole tutorial video,
I recorded one that lasted two hours.
Each step has never been skipped.
Including adding a lot of subtitle videos.
So now everyone is just a little bit of understanding.
Just do it.
Then here, the number is selected as 3.
Because it is a group of three lines.
Then just print it and simulate it.
You can see that this version is folded.
After folding, we will copy it.
Then after using the sewing machine,
When this tool is folded,
It seems that it can't be identified.
It's because of our lines.
It didn't choose to align the panels and add points.
Because it doesn't divide.
It's just the inner line to the end.
But it didn't cut it off according to the inner line.
So we have to cut it off.
After cutting it off, you can use this sewing machine.
Select the waist side first.
Then select the skirt side.
There will be subtitles.
Then when I sewed here, I forgot.
Which direction should I sew along?
Oh, I remember.
Then I suddenly remembered.
Oh, it's this direction.
So it's not just you guys.
Only when you are doing it, there will be some.
When you suddenly forget.
When we do it, we often forget.
Then we cancel the hard drawing.
Because I don't need it to be folded again.
Then I found that there is a place where I forgot to sew.
In fact, I often forget to sew the clothes.
Then I looked at it again.
Is there anything to change in this skirt?
I found that this skirt is a bit too short.
Just lengthen it a little bit.
Okay.
Then I will activate it.
Then I found that the waist belt is still falling down.
I'll take it off a little bit.
Okay.
Then I will put the hemline of the shirt back in.
Here I put the hemline back in.
After putting it back in, you can see that this shirt is back to the original measurement.
Then here I changed its fabric to Cotton Garbine.
This fabric is often used to make cardigan.
It can also be used to make cardigan.
There are also some harder shirts.
Then I may hide the side panels of the skirt.
Then take a look at this shirt.
Because if you don't hide it, you can't choose the inside.
I will hide the outside panels.
Then take it off.
Tighten the clothes a little bit.
Then because the skirt is made of the same fabric as the shirt.
It will look too hard.
So I changed it to Cotton Garbine.
Cotton Garbine is more soft.
It is more suitable for models.
Then I will take a look at this shirt.
Can I hide it again?
Because I think it has a little more wrinkles.
Then I thought about it.
What should I do?
Anyway, I was thinking at that time.
Oh, am I going to change the shirt inside again?
I thought about it for a long time.
I finally remembered it.
Forget it.
Let's add a shirt.
Because I actually didn't have any concept before I made clothes.
I usually think about where to do where.
Then, for example, like this side.
I think this curve is a little too crooked.
I changed it to a straight line again.
Then I think this shirt seems to look too high.
I will change the position of the shirt again.
Like this.
After changing it.
I think its size seems to be OK.
Then I will open the model again.
Give it a shrink.
Here everyone must be thinking.
Why did I shrink this shrink back again?
Because I want to make its jacket.
Then I was thinking at that time.
Hmm.
Like such a little rich woman.
What do they wear in winter?
Does she wear a sweater directly outside the shirt?
Then, oh.
Wear a sweater jacket outside the shirt.
Then I think the sweater jacket is a little too cold.
I just want to say.
Oh, let's add a sweater jacket for her.
Then, in the version released by Cologne.
Because she has the previous interrogation.
Then I will enlarge her sleeves.
This is soon to be able to put on this dress to wear out.
Then, the rope away.
Because the general sweater jacket
is relatively loose and loose.
I was actually at the beginning.
I want to make a suit set.
So I was thinking at that time.
what kind of sweater the little sister in the uniform wears.
Because I don't wear sweaters very often myself.
And then after I copied this layer,
it's actually the shirt inside.
And then I re-activated its sleeves,
so that I can see it more conveniently.
Is the size of the top of the shirt suitable?
And then I think the bottom of the shirt,
you can see here,
is it very tight?
It feels like it's already bent.
Sometimes when you're making clothes,
if you feel that this shirt
has been bent from here to under the arm,
then is the size here going to be modified?
So here I will pull the position of this point down,
which is to pull this point down,
and put it here.
After pulling it down,
I feel that it's bent on the side again.
And then the size seems to be a bit wrong.
Because actually,
the curve of the sweater
is not that obvious,
the curve of the curve.
So I fixed the curve on the side again.
After fixing it,
I looked at it again.
I still feel that this sweater
seems to be a bit weird.
And then I basically do that kind of
subconscious operation,
that is,
I'm used to dragging that
board
to drag and look at them.
And then I looked at the sweater
and let him wear it again.
And then I finally found out
what was strange about it.
Because its shoulder is too narrow.
The point of its shoulder is the shoulder of the shirt.
Generally, the sweater is very loose.
Its shoulders can't be as narrow as the shirt.
So I adjusted the length of this line of the shoulder.
In the same process,
I still
re-activated the sleeve.
Plus, I think the fabric of the sweater
will be softer.
I didn't use the fabric of the shirt
for the sweater anymore.
And then I thought,
why don't I make it
a sweater that looks a bit like
a bat sleeve?
The characteristic of a bat sleeve
is that its shoulders
are usually low.
That is, its shoulders will be very long.
In fact,
now it's a bit like
talking about
fashion knowledge.
The shoulder of the sweater
is like this.
Why is the shoulder of the sweater
going down here?
It's because the shoulder of the sweater
just now
is bent up here, right?
Then you put the point of the shoulder
along this line down,
it will be a bit more
close to the model.
The point of the shoulder is
to match the length of the two shoulder lines.
After matching,
it's still the same.
Adjust the position.
I look at it,
I feel that
this circle is a bit
too curved.
Because
it's a bit
out of line
with the model's curve.
So I'm going to
change it again
to fix its curve.
This part may really
look like
it's not very interesting
when I put it on.
It's okay.
The back will
become more interesting.
Then I still have to
fix the curve
on the side.
Then I fix it,
fix it,
I feel that
it's really tired.
For the back,
if you have a back
in a 3D environment,
it will not participate in the simulation.
Its powder line will be lost,
its deformation will be,
that is,
this panel
will not deform.
A few days ago,
we posted an article
on WeChat.
You may not have seen it.
I also posted
it on Bilibili.
Then like
the sleeves here,
because just now
the sleeves
are very long.
It's longer
than one.
Because we have
the shoulder line here,
is it a piece
that goes down?
Then like the sleeves,
it also has to be long
and move down.
So that its overall
length will not change.
Then just now
this curve,
it is because
it is to fit
the curve of the sleeves
before,
so it is very
rough.
Then now
our sleeves
are very flat,
so we have to
make this curve
become more
soft,
too
flat
a little
and then
let it side
this corner
is a right corner.
Now you can see
through our
change to the curve
and the shape
of the sleeves
is not it
now the sweater
becomes a
shoulder sleeve
is
relatively
loose
sleeves
that sweater
and then
I want to
give it
to cut
the collar
because
the original
sweater
the position of the collar
makes me feel like
it is
I do not like
this kind of design
I designed
or a V collar
to see
a relatively
large collar
and then
I will
according to
this
sewing line
because the sewing line
before it is
long
and then
add a point
in the sewing line
position
so that I can
make sure
its front and back
shoulder
sewing
is the same
good
finished
after
you can see
now our
sweater
will become
a
relatively loose
and then shoulder
down
a sweater
and then
I think
I still want
the sweater
inside the skirt
so I
give the skirt
set
a layer
layer set as
so that the sweater
will automatically
fit into the skirt
inside
and then
it is the same
hide the skirt
and then
put the sweater
inside
a little bit
we just
take it off slowly
and we can
take it off
inside
no
BGM
you will not
feel too quiet
will not
his sweater
in this position
because I tried
this sweater
at most
will only be stuck
in this position
will not go down
because I
was looking at
a reference picture of Taobao
it is like this
relatively
loose
oh
then don't
BGM
I was going to put
something good luck
like this
more New Year's atmosphere
because now
only I am alone
in the company
it is very quiet
you know
it sounds
weird
and then
I will choose
the neckline
of the neckline
of the inner line
because
it is very
if the sweater
is only one
pattern
it will look
very boring
really
fake
I just
like
him
to stop
in this position
and then
cut the thread
to deny it
cut the sweater
and then
you can see
just
this sweater
here
is not down
and then
here
I gave him
added
two circles of
elastic
elastic value
must be set to
so that
it can ensure
this
line
it is straight
just
this line
is not a little bend
and then
it looks a little
easy to fall
once
it reaches
it will not
fall
because it has to
maintain
its original
length
it can not
transform
and then
I think
the position
of the button
is a little
awkward
I will move
the button
up
after
moving
it
I will
take a look
at its
simulation
effect
and then
reduce the
length
why
because of
the outer
layer
of clothing
your
strength
should be
low enough
grid
material
enough
clothes
inside
will not
be easy
to wear
from inside
and then
it is the same
to remove
all the
plates
elastic
value
to 100
can
maintain
its original length
and then
it will
naturally
slide
here
if
it is
like this
for these two sides
to use
the elasticity
it may
be stretched
to 300 mm
now
it must
only have
200 mm
then
it will
slowly
wear
back
and wear
until
it can
meet
this line
is 200 mm
200 mm
then
it is the same
pull
its
sweater
just look
and then
freeze
after
it freezes
I want to
make a shirt
not a shirt
make a
bow tie
usually
has a
that
has a line
it is
usually
a long
long
line
what are you referring to
I think
the sewing line
is
you do
a lot
you know
how to sew
this
I can't teach
it
because
this question
is not
often
asked by
friends
and then
after
drawing
two panels
it is also
sewed
to the collar
here
and then
reduce
the
resistance
and then
use the line
to move
to the
seam line
you can quickly
move these two panels
to the collar
here
you don't have to use
any arrangement
panels
and positioning balls
and then
you will see
it will shake
because the outside
of this panel
is frozen
in a frozen state
this
panel
will not pass
over
and then
you see
even if I set
the layer
it won't work
and then
I will talk about
the part
of the bag
later
and then
you will find
I
I used layers
for the collar
here
right?
in theory
this panel
should be
below
this collar
but it
doesn't
why?
because
do you remember
when we saw it
this collar
is facing
the back
now
we are
on the surface
of the
canvas
actually
because
after opening the
canvas
no matter
if it is
positive or
negative
it is
white
you can't
see it
so
in this
case
I suggest
you to
open
the non-canvas
canvas
otherwise
you will
make mistakes
like me
I was
confused
when I did
this
oh
it is because
I didn't open
the single layer
I opened the double layer
later
since
you can't
pull it in
you just
put the collar
in the
position
it doesn't matter
if you don't understand
as long as
you remember
this method
is not good
just change
another method
I will
show you
the document
this is
what we
talked about
in the previous video
if you open
the single layer
you will
find
it is
facing
the back
the collar
here
eh
the collar
here
is facing
the back
the layer
it is
to identify
this kind of
front
facing
panel
if you
use
if you set
the layer
then
this
panel
it will
work
at this time
if there is
a panel
below this layer
it will
confirm
oh
you didn't
touch my
front
anyway
I won't
identify you
understand
this is
the layer
is only
on the front
it is
to identify
the front
like the collar
here
it is
facing
the back
it won't
work
then
like here
for example
there is
a collar
I will
change
its size
oh
it's ok
you just
try it
you will
understand
just
remember
the layer
is facing
the back
um
anyway
the layer
this tool
is
the back
facing
the panel
you can't use
the layer
it must
be facing
the front
like clothes
this position
is ok
collar here
is not ok
then
create two
longer
wider
panels
as
the position of
the butterfly
the other panels
are also
to make it
easier for me
to make the butterfly
the panels
of the butterfly
are smaller
so we
use a
5mm
and add
two pins
you may
wonder
why
I add pins
here
to use
pins
I can
flatten it
first
when flattening
I add
the rings
in the middle
it is very
convenient
after having one layer
I can cut
one layer
it is a
three-dimensional
butterfly
then
apply the
shrink
to make it
a narrower
panel
because
the middle
of the
normal
pattern
is
very tight
if
you
let it
add
the ring
outside
it will
be
inconvenient
we
will
cut
the
bottom
to make it
tight
like this
so this
is the
front
and back
this
is the
front
right
and
this
is the
back
and
this
is the
back
this
is the
front
and
First, pull the bow very, very flat
Then, add the ring
You can see that I'm adding the ring here
OK, after adding it, reduce the diameter of the ring
Now, is it more convenient to sew it up?
Because your bow is flat now
Ah, yes, you can just cut the bow
Cut the bow
There is a cut on the right side of the selected version
OK
It's almost Chinese New Year, and you're not allowed to put it on
You can put it on tomorrow
Then turn on the simulation
Is it fast now?
Because this version is flat just now
It's easier to add the small rectangle in the middle
If it's like this now
It's easier to produce
Unstable problems
This is how the butterfly knot is completed
In fact, the butterfly knot is really fast
And it's very convenient
You just have to remember to pull the version flat first
Then I made him a jacket
About how to make a jacket
You can see in the back
There will be a tutorial video
There will be
In fact, there is no difference with changing the sweater
Then here I add two fake stitches
Set the length of his line
So we can control this version
Is the distance between the two versions
What is the advantage of controlling this distance?
When you change the action
This dress
The distance between these two pieces will never change
Then you can see just now
Hana turned into a bald head in an instant
That's because we changed the bald head to make him a hat
Why is the butterfly knot three layers?
Because this butterfly knot is like this
You can see that there are three pieces here, right?
These two pieces are one layer
And this one is a flat version
I just copied a layer out of convenience
Can you understand?
Then you can see we changed an action
Just use the pose form to block in
Then change the action
Then the position of the clothes also changed
After changing
I'm thinking I'm going to put his hand in the pocket
Yes
Then I will freeze this pocket plate first
In fact, I am now letting the pocket plate not move
Then let the clothes go to the plate to sew
This is more convenient
Then there will not be any problems with wearing
That's like fingers here
Because the model's finger net is generally more and more thin
So when facing a big piece of clothing
Because of the grid of clothing
It is not delicate enough
It will have a problem like this
One is that we want to reduce the particle diameter of the clothing
There is another one
Just take a look
Is there any board around it
Let this board not be able to pass through
For example, like me
I'm here because of the skirt board
I'm frozen
So he can't pass through
Because there is a collision between the fabric and the fabric
Then after wearing it
I will delete the fake red needle
Yes
In this way, you can let this coat
Naturally have some scattered effects
So you can imagine
If we want to put our hands in MD
If you want to put your hands through a pocket
Then what you have to do is
You have to put the pocket cloth first
Instead of putting your hands in
In this case, our ordinary imagination is not the same
We have to speed up
After that, make socks
It's very convenient to make socks
You just draw a rectangle first
Then change its size little by little
The method of making socks
In fact, in our previous Christmas special
Also talked about
Just draw a rectangle first
Then talk about the rest later
I was thinking about those
Because I want to make one myself
It's a little bit of a New Year's Eve
New Year's Eve is the one that is more ancient
That is, it was actually 12 years ago
In China
Some of the clothes they wear are popular
I feel like it used to be a very popular pair of socks
So I'm going in the direction of the pair of socks
Then I think this sock is always going to fall out of the shoes
Not very good-looking
So I put it on the top and bottom of this board
Make it narrower
Then lower the chest of the chest
Make it more smooth
In fact, it's just to repeat the adjustment
Repeat the adjustment
Look at the position of his pile
Is it reasonable
Is it the position I want
Wow, I'm really in this section
I spent a lot of time on this sock
I've been looking at this sock all the time
How to change and change
I don't think I can change it
I don't like it
Not satisfied
Then I adjusted it for a long time
Finally it looks a little more eye-catching
Then don't learn from me
I forgot to change the action here
So I changed the action first
Then the fake socks
If you do it, it's best to wear socks like this
You wear it first and then change the action
Otherwise it will be very troublesome
Then just make him a bag
What I want is to let him have another bag of leather on his hand
So I'm here
Sew this belt
Just let him put it on the motorcycle
Then add two pins
Right click
Oh no
The model is on the floor
Maybe it's my posture
This is actually not a big deal
Then change a fabric for him
Here I use leather fabric
The leather fabric
Because it's harder
So I'll do it alone
Reduce its bending strength a little bit
Otherwise his belt looks like it's going to be hard
Then freeze this board
Then draw
I want to make him a heart-shaped bag for him
Then actually the size of this board
I drew it casually
I'm all referring to the effect in the 3D window
I think it's OK
Just draw it directly
This bag also has nothing
No reference picture
Then copy another layer and put it over
In fact, you can use a symmetrical board here
I didn't think so much at the time
I just wanted to sew it directly
Then in fact
It's still quite troublesome later
So that's it
Everyone has a vacation
Then I'm making this long strip
This long strip
It is actually used to sew
In the middle of these two heart-shaped boards
As a thickness of the bag
It counts
I speed up here very quickly
Take these two lines, the inner lines, and take a look at their positions.
After matching the top and the bottom, use the 3D sewing machine to sew the two sides together.
After sewing it together, let's see where it's sewn.
Oh, it's sewn in the right place. That's good.
Let's do a few more simulations, and then we can hang it up.
So actually, making a bag is also very difficult.
As long as you have the brain power, you'll know what the bag should look like.
For example, no matter what the shape is on the side, the middle must be a rectangle.
Unless you want to make the side of the bag to be a T-shape.
Otherwise, the middle one is usually a rectangle.
It looks good. This bag is what I thought it would look like.
Then we'll make a circle around the edge of the bag.
For the edge of the bag, you have to reduce the diameter of the bag to make a circle around the edge of the bag.
After making the edge of the bag, you have to sew the side of the bag up.
Add some extra pressure to it.
So that it can stick to the side of the bag.
When I made this step, I realized,
Oh, why am I doing this?
Why don't I make it symmetrical?
It makes me have to sew it again and again.
It's very tiring.
But then I thought,
Oh, never mind.
Never mind.
I shouldn't...
Why is it suddenly wrinkled?
It's because I added a circle around the edge of the bag.
This circle around the edge of the bag...
I also like the edge of the bag.
This circle around the edge of the bag,
this rectangle,
so this circle,
it's long.
So this circle,
do you sew a lot of strips onto a very short line?
If you do this,
it will make some wrinkles.
Then it's a bag.
It's also very convenient to make a bag.
You just...
You just sew it with a bag.
After I put it on my hand, I'll change the
pattern, and then add the buttons.
Because I don't have much reference for bag bags.
Because I don't really buy big bags.
My bags are all small bags, not practical bags.
And then I'm thinking about what the bag bag here is like.
I feel like there are some buttons here.
And then I made a round button for it.
And then after adding the buttons,
Oh, it's so fast here.
I'm going to draw an inner line.
And then I want to add a day button in the middle.
So I'm going to sew the two sides together.
And then I'm going to make sure that the
number of buttons is equal to one.
And then it's going to go down.
You can see that on this sheet, its particle building is one,
and its side curves are very soft, because there are more net blocks.
As for this side, its particle building is very large,
and it's very hard here, and it doesn't seem to be soft enough.
But it will have a rough texture.
I really made it fast.
Then the bag is about here.
How do you think?
That's about it.
After that, we'll make a date button.
The method to make a date button is very simple.
Just dig a hole in the middle,
and then add a rendering thickness to it.
Then find this version and use the position to set it here.
If you use 1, does it look like it?
No.
If you use 1, it depends on the size of your version.
If your version is small,
it doesn't matter if your version is 1.
Look at me.
My whole set of clothes is actually the lowest,
which is 5 or 10.
I only use 1 on very small versions.
And then this button,
I actually made it with a version.
As long as you set its physical properties a little harder,
it's fine.
And then,
like the belt here,
make it round.
Because generally,
belts like this are not hard.
And then I thought,
this bag doesn't look good with a round button.
So I changed it to a hat-shaped button.
And then set its physical properties to the top 3,
no, the top 6 to 100.
The rest to 0.
That's it.
And then fix its shape a little bit.
So in fact,
during the whole process of making the bag,
the longest time I spent was making this button.
And then I made it a scarf.
A lot of my friends asked me how to make a scarf.
We can demonstrate how to make a scarf.
First, arrange it on the collar here.
And then you can see that this scarf is relatively wide.
And then I'll shrink it a little bit.
Is it going to be narrower now?
It's narrower than it actually is.
So we're going to use the shrink tool,
this function,
so that the collar here is tied up first.
The day control is thick.
I added the dye thickness.
And then just drag it a little bit.
Let this scarf here,
just remember to tighten it up a little bit.
And then you can see that I'm going to shrink it again.
So now this scarf is much narrower than it actually is.
It looks like this scarf is narrow right now.
The advantage of doing this is that we can use this method to make the scarf very tight.
So that when we put the shrink back to its original 100,
the tight place will be tightened directly,
and it will become a tight state.
No, I'm just going to put the day control here directly.
It can be simulated.
Because I made it with a board.
And then in the process, I'll add some pins.
And then the pins are actually a bit like our hands.
And then in the process, you have to make sure that the fabric is enough.
Don't let the fabric transform into a large shape.
It stretches very well.
If it stretches very well,
then you will wear this knot directly.
Can you understand?
Just treat the fabric gently.
Don't make it transform very well.
And then shorten its width a little bit.
And then make it a little longer on the side.
Now the scarf is fixed with a pin.
Pull a small knot.
After pulling, we turn the shrink from 40 to 60.
Does this scarf become wider?
It gradually approaches its original width.
If you just pull it,
the reason is basically because your fabric length is too short.
Make sure the fabric is loose.
Understand?
Just don't pull it to transform.
Usually the fabric starts to shake.
It means that your width is not enough.
Here, pull the scarf to the position you want.
For example, if I pull it to here, I think it's OK.
I will add a pin to it.
Then adjust the position of it.
It won't transform after a day.
Because I just said that I have changed its physical properties.
Physical properties, you have to set all the first six items to 100.
If you set all the other items to 0, it won't transform.
Then here, its shrink is still 80.
In fact, is its width now a little bit narrower than its actual width?
Then I will add some pins to it.
Then use the pin tool to double stitch along a line.
It will go straight along both sides.
Add a whole row.
The inner line.
Then when I return its shrink to 100,
did you notice that in a moment,
there are a lot of these very similar wrinkles?
After having these very similar wrinkles,
delete these pins.
Then shape it.
These wrinkles will be added.
Can you understand?
When you shrink it to 80,
it doesn't have the original width.
Then you use the pin to lock it on both sides.
Then add the material in the middle.
It will become like this now.
After making the scarf,
it's actually time to make the tail.
For example, like the bag here.
I think this bag looks a bit monotonous.
I'll cut it and sew it up.
Then it's actually the same old three.
After cutting and sewing,
you have to check if its sewing line has fallen off.
If there is,
you have to sew it up again.
After sewing,
I want to make the bag's inner line.
For the scarf process,
there will be a specific process in the video that will be uploaded later.
It's an unaccelerated process.
You can watch that video later.
After choosing all the inner lines,
align them to the outer line of the fabric.
Now we have the sewing line.
Then after sewing two layers,
look at the model,
it will have...
Oh, I remember.
This is because I found that my sewing line is broken.
Because after cutting the sewing line,
the sewing line is broken.
Oh, I didn't delete this part.
Forget it.
Because after the cologne is stored,
it will look like this.
It will look like this.
I don't know if you can feel it.
It doesn't matter if you can't feel it.
You can feel it in a moment.
I will use the elastic for these inner lines.
After using the elastic,
you can see that
there will be some
creases,
and some shrinkage effects.
This will have some
cotton,
thin cotton effect.
Layer cologne.
Yes, layer cologne.
Whether it's the outer or inner cologne layer,
it's okay.
Then I will give them some
positive pressure and negative pressure.
Then you can see that
this bag looks like it's inflated.
This way,
it will have the effect of inflating cotton.
And then,
I will put it on the cologne.
I will put its waist here.
I will give it a little bit of color.
Because I was thinking
that I was going to make some patterns for it.
I will change the color.
And then,
I will take a look at how I match the color.
My pattern
will be made later.
It will be made in other software.
I was thinking that
this year is the Year of the Ox.
But,
I was thinking that
I still have to make it a bit cuter.
So,
I still matched it with a pink color.
Actually,
I will use a simple color block
to define the color of the whole set of clothes.
Oh,
about how to add texture to this piece.
In the complete version of the video after this,
there is one.
I will jump over here.
It's just because
my texture is only
only drawn in PS.
The next step is
how to make a cow's foot.
I first draw an inner line.
And then,
making a cow's foot is actually
a very magical method.
And then,
I will imagine
what the curve of the side of the cow's foot is like.
After drawing this version,
remember to reduce the particle resolution.
Otherwise,
the curve will not work.
If you can't get some patterns,
you have to try more.
Try more.
And then,
I will use the leather fabric for the cow's foot.
You can see that
after using the leather fabric,
this version is
fat and round.
This way,
it's not easy to transform.
And then,
I will make another layer.
I will set it as a joint version.
Wow,
I added a lot of speed here.
And then,
I will sew it here.
There are some clothes and pants
that I don't know how to style.
You can search it online.
And then,
you can just
search them in the form of your background.
And then,
the cow's foot is done.
Isn't it amazing?
After you add the leather fabric,
the cow's foot will be sewn up.
After you sew it up,
it will bulge.
This is the characteristic of leather fabric.
It will bulge.
And then,
I will think about
the curve of the cow's foot.
Because I feel that
this one foot
looks bare.
It doesn't have
the texture of a cow's foot.
What is the function of joint version?
The joint version is like this.
After you set up the joint version,
if you change the shape of one of the versions,
whether you change the shape
or what,
or add points,
each version will be changed at the same time.
And then,
align it to the outline of the version.
if you double-click an inner line on a version,
you can choose all the inner lines on this version.
And then,
here is also the outline of the version.
cut a layer to the outside.
Well,
does the inner line here
have the shape of the cow's foot?
And then,
you can add more details on it.
Next,
select all the inner lines
and give it a folding angle.
For example,
260 degrees.
It will be folded in here.
The curve.
That's because
I've seen a lot of
those games.
I think
the cow's feet
are generally like this.
There will be a certain
texture of the curve line.
So I added these inner lines to it.
That's 260 degrees.
For example, if the inner line is set to a folding angle,
if this angle is less than 180, this line will protrude outward.
If it is greater than 180, this line will bend inward.
If it is like a bull's foot, it will generally bend inward.
How to judge the angle?
If you want to have a curve,
for example, like a bull's foot, it will bend inward,
just like the angle of a knife.
Then it must be greater than 180 degrees.
If it protrudes outward, it will be a folding angle.
Understand?
Then here are some all angles.
For all angles, you have to set it to be greater than 180.
Then I will look at it,
and see if the angle is okay.
The size is right, right?
Then I thought about it.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Then I will fold it out first.
I will fold the OBJ out first.
Then I will fold the OBJ in.
Then here, the process of making this set of clothes is over.
If you have any questions, you can ask.
Then I dyed my hair in Vray.
I dyed my hair with Vray's own hair dye.
Then I will cut out this picture.
Let me see if I have an strobe.
Is it this one?
Oh, it's MD Minimum.
Yes.
Otherwise, why should we call it MD, and not MD
Look, my strobe ...
This one.
As you can see, these are some of the patterns I drew.
I added a few flowers at the time.
I think this one looks better.
The pink one looks better.
MD is a Korean app.
Can't Korean apps be distributed in China?
Yes, they can.
OBJ is imported in the form of a copy.
This one is my favorite.
I'm going to use a reflective material on this side
to give it a bit of a leathery effect.
As for the fur,
I can't make it very detailed.
You can just look at it roughly.
I didn't change the brightness or anything.
As for this side,
I'm going to make it thicker here.
It looks thicker like this.
As for the pattern,
I'm going to use an oblique pattern.
As for the sweater,
I'm going to use a sweater material.
As for the skirt,
I'm going to use a substance material.
It looks like chocolate.
Yes, I also think it looks like chocolate.
It feels a bit like...
It gives people a feeling of sweetness.
At the time, I was...
How did the fabric of the sweater come about?
You mean...
the pattern?
Yes.
I made the fur with V-Ray.
I drew the pattern myself.
I hand-drawn the pattern myself.
The pattern of the cow.
Why is the leg so well done?
I don't understand.
The leg is...
Are you talking about its effect?
I don't know.
V-Ray...
V-Ray's own...
The...
I...
I just slightly changed some lighting settings.
And then I didn't change the texture of the skin.
I haven't given it the texture of the four-sided scattered color.
I think if I use the four-sided scattered color,
the skin should be a little more transparent.
Anyway, V-Ray's dye is...
It's more...
It's more convenient.
And then I added some bright lines to the bag.
So that it will be along the seam line.
It has some...
The effect of sewing.
Actually, I still have some details that I haven't done.
For example, I didn't make it tight here.
No.
The face and...
The legs are not the same.
It's just that...
There's a big light here on my face.
It's against my face.
The shoes...
I just removed the pattern of the shoes.
I think the pattern of the shoes...
That...
The pattern doesn't really match this outfit.
So I just removed the texture of the shoes.
I just used a single color.
Yes.
The face is just a big light.
How to make the outfit tight?
You have to reduce the surface of the model.
So that the air wall around the model will reduce its thickness.
Secondly,
You have to make the panel thick.
Not thick.
The thickness of the bump.
The panel itself has a thickness of bump.
You have to reduce it to zero.
So that it can be tight.
Our model.
Do you guys have any questions about MD?
You can also ask.
Now you can play the background music.
I've been preparing the background music for a long time.
I have to play it.
I have to play the background music.
If I don't play the background music...
There are a lot of questions.
You can ask me.
In the lower left corner,
Our official group can ask questions in the official group.
Everyone usually answers.
I was thinking about the Chinese New Year.
And then...
At that time...
At that time, our colleague asked...
She asked if there were any traditional Chinese clothes.
I said Hanfu.
But I've already done Hanfu before.
And then...
Cheap cheapskates.
Cheap cheapskates were also done last time.
When the new feature was released.
The teacher took a long vacation.
Miao...
Wow, Miao's fashion is too difficult.
Miao's fashion mainly has a lot of accessories.
You know?
That accessory is something I'm not good at.
I can't do all the hard materials.
There will be replays.
There will be...
I actually think that
The lighting in MD is very beautiful.
But when I go outside, the lighting is not very beautiful.
How to make a leather vest?
It's best not to make it a little bit hard in MD.
But it doesn't matter if it's leather.
Just use a leather fabric for it.
I'll look for it.
There should be one in my bag.
It's leather.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's useless.
There's a full green leather.
Trim full green leather.
This fabric.
It's leather.
Do you make men's clothes?
Yes.
It's just that I usually...
Oh, really?
That's what you said.
I rarely make men's clothes.
Because I think men's clothes are more boring.
A...
So I usually throw men's clothes to Jinmi.
Jinmi.
Then let Jinmi prepare a tutorial video.
Can MD make shoes?
Yes.
MD...
I've made shoes.
But you have to do it in a weird way.
And not all shoes can do it.
It's just...
It's just a little bit time-consuming.
It feels too hard to adjust the pressure to make leather vest.
Well, if you make leather vest,
you can lower its bending strength a little bit.
A leather vest has a feature.
That is, its stretching performance is not very good.
But it...
Because the leather is a little soft.
So its stretching performance is not too bad.
Full green leather.
It's 30-30.
It's just right.
But for full green leather,
its bending strength is very high.
Let me show you.
This fabric.
Its bending strength is 90.
What does 90 mean?
It means you hold this piece of fabric.
It won't go down.
It won't fall down.
Jinmi also made it.
You have to lower its bending strength a little bit.
Jinmi was a little bit like it in the hunter episode.
Are you talking about the one with the wool hat?
I think this is okay, too.
Let me prepare it after the year.
After the year, because it's really...
There are some things.
There are some things to do.
Things to do.
It's a new version of the thing.
Now do you think that Mammoth Designer 10 just came out?
Mammoth Designer 10.5 is coming out soon.
So...
After the new version comes out,
I'm going to prepare 10.5.
In fact, it's suitable for lockpicking.
Lockpicking, because you have to lockpick.
Because it's a lot of small things.
There are a lot of small metals that are added together
It won't be as hard as the fabric
It's better to do it in other software
After doing it, you can use the model form to pour it into AMD
This way there will be a physical collision
This is better
10.5
Not hard, not hard
Why are you all calling my sister
I'm only 18
Why are you all calling my sister Xuanyu
I'm going to cry
Do you guys have any more questions?
You can ask me
You can ask me any questions you want
Including questions about using AMD
Oh, that's good
So you're 17
That's fine
You can ask me anything you want
And I'll think about it
Do you guys have any more questions about using AMD?
Do you have any more questions about using AMD?
Any questions about using AMD?
Let's put in a good day
Physical attributes, we can talk about that
In terms of physical attributes, we actually have a video about physical attributes
I'll wait a little bit for Mingxian's question
Because I don't know which part of the question you asked Mingxian
But I didn't put any physical attributes in the costume, so I don't think it's a big deal
And then, for example, the gold tail sand wall here
It will affect your costume
Let me think, let me find you some clothes
For example, there is a set of clothes, right?
If we increase the strength of the gold tail sand wall
Then its stretchability will be relatively poor
It feels like this set of clothes is a big deal
You will feel that this fabric becomes very hard
And then it has a lot of fine, small wrinkles
It looks a bit like that
It's the kind of wrinkle that's like a breeze
It won't be as soft as it was just now
On the contrary, if you reduce the strength of the gold tail sand wall
Its stretchability will be better
Overall, it looks like there will be some hammering
And then, after that, is the stretchability
The stretchability actually affects the stretchability of the costume
Is it hard or soft?
Wait a minute, let me put it back to the default fabric
When the stretchability is relatively high
This fabric will look more like a leather
It will look like this
You see, these wrinkles will be stretched
And the number of wrinkles will be less
The wrinkles will be bigger
It looks a bit hard
If you turn it over, it's closer to silk
If it's silk, its wrinkles will be thinner
What about the rest of these
You can take a look at our previous video
There is a video in the video
The
Because it doesn't really affect the real physical impact
The reason I put in the adhesives is because
Uh, adhesives are easier to locate
Because adhesives have that
Locating function, right?
The idea of hard leather bags
There is no idea
Hard leather bags are just
Just do what you do
Because I don't do bags that much
I usually make cute bags
As long as you have a version
Just do what you do according to your supply list
And we still recommend the clothing industry to use clothes
Next question
How do you know how to use adhesives?
Adhesives are white
I don't know where you don't know how to use adhesives
Don't you know how to add adhesives?
If you add adhesives, use this tool
Adhesives
Then click along this side
There will be an adhesives
New machine industry
You still have to make hard bags
You just have to give it the bend intensity
Just add it up
I actually don't know what gold is
Gold is something
What is gold?
Is gold the middle?
Will there be something in the middle?
If that's the case
When you're making it
You sew a small plate in the middle
Go in
and then increase the thickness of the conflict, it will have that kind of
um, it will have a protruding effect
Hey, I don't have the right place to add the thread. Oh, here it is
And then the thread, it has a 3D, you can open it
and it will have the effect of denying
But this hair line doesn't seem to be easy to understand
There will be some problems
Round-shaped envelopes, oh, you can just use a string, a string, a string
I thought you were asking what, this, this, this
Double click it, and then there will be an envelope
Usually people who use MD are in the C-level industry
or in the gaming industry
Because the clothing industry is still involved in production
Let's change the song
This song, I feel like today is
is
is the last day of the year
Use this
The string
Click it
Double click it
There will be an envelope
Use this 3D window
The tool of the string
And then click it
You just add this circle along the line
And then double click
There will be a string
Single click is to determine the direction
That is, the direction of the side you sew
How to change models
You just double click to open
You can change
Because today I
Oh, I feel that you will definitely find that I have been blinking
Because today's thread has been on for a long time
I can't see things clearly
In fact, I feel that the most difficult thing is to go around the micro-blog
I think it's okay
You said it was a scarf, right?
This is you first change the rectangle
Then arrange it well
Then there is no need to use other versions
Just freeze
Activate
The interface of the string
You have to do it again in other 3D software
There is no way to deal with this on the side of Marus Designer
I don't know if this is enough with the scarf length
This length is a lot shorter
In fact, when I look at it
I usually don't care about its length
Really
Change to a different figure
It's like this
I don't know if you know
Our new feature is called Shifu
For example, let's take a look
Now this set of clothes is worn on our model
Then
I don't know if you want to change the size
For example, let's wear it first
After wearing it
We can change a model
Because the default model in Marus Designer
It's all of its own size
I've already worn it
If you want to wear it, you have to use this tool to create it
Do it
This is in our new feature introduction
After that
You just click on the automatic dress
Then just wait a little bit
This is the size of the size
It won't change
Wait a little bit
You will hear that I got a fan on my computer
Because this fan on this CPU
Is quite high
Because I have the Schneider model
My overall end paint is perfectly clean
I want to see if I can put on clothes for animals
Oh! Look, if the size is not right, it will look like this
So usually, you still have to use the auto-adjustable version
And then click OK
Wait for it to change its size
If you want to put on clothes for animals
You have to put on clothes that are a little more clever
There's a recording today
It's written on the bottom left corner
There will be a recording
I'm so mad
Oh, if the scale is set to 2, it will...
The simulation will take longer
Like right now, look at my whole set of clothes
The scale is set to 8 or 10
If you use the auto-adjustable version
It will take quite a while
About 1 or 2 minutes
You just have to wait for it to go to the background
I feel like right now, it still looks very weird
After that, you just have to wait one more turn
The four legs are so difficult
There are more tails and stuff
That's because the position of the legs is different
How do you do semi-transparent?
The fabric...
Oh, I know
Because there are lines on my clothes
So it takes a long time
It's okay if you breathe
Look, isn't it?
Isn't it amazing?
Brothers, put the magic on the fairness
This skirt...
The size of this skirt
Suddenly became the size of Hana
If you want to breathe outside the pants
You have to reduce the shrinkage of the pants first
Then make the pants into a tight pants
Then add breathing
After adding breathing
Use...
Use a fake red needle to fix it on top of you
Magic
Isn't it amazing?
It's magic
Then be sure not to have a line
If there is a line, it will be a little bit stuck
Semi-transparent is like this
You just have to reduce its transparency a little bit
Just fine
See if there is any problem
Just reduce its transparency
Use different fabrics for it
Then the right side can reduce its transparency
Just fine
In addition
If you have an alpha picture
Or RGB
RGB
If you have a sticker
If you have a transparent picture
You can also click here
After setting, put the gold line
Yes
After setting, you put the gold line
The shrinkage of the gold thread is changed back
Because gold thread is up to you
It's your clothes
For example, you choose this with this editing text
This direction is golden
This direction is tail
If we want to turn this dress into a neckline
Then you must change the shrinkage here, right?
So that her dress can become tight
Otherwise, if you are in this direction
Then is her dress just short separately
But it's not tight
The purple round stem on the left side is to bring the belt
I don't know what kind of clothes Zouzhu is wearing
Because I haven't seen our wedding photos
I know there's Zouzhu, but I don't know what her belt looks like
I'll search it up and take a look
I know her name is Sasuke
I'm looking at her belt, why is her...
Yes, the old version of the new version of the project, the old version, there's a high probability that you won't be able to open it
Because if you use some special features
Oh, I saw Sasuke's belt
If you want to do it in MD, you can do it
But...
It's just...
It's very troublesome, and you have to do it for a long time
ZB doesn't really know how to do it
You have to imagine it
Sasuke's belt
You said it was like this, right?
This belt
It has to be a round shape
And it's harder to deal with the flow
This is one
And there's another one below
Just like I'm doing the cow's feet
Like this cow's feet
It has to be two pieces
See if my cow's feet are two pieces
It has to be round
Sasuke's belt is also
And then you have to turn around in the middle
It's a little bit more troublesome
Because I used to do it in MD
The three-dimensional horse rope
It's like this
Rolled up
Very tired
More troublesome
MD can't do the flow
You can't do it with a sticker
Is there a simple way to do the knot?
The easiest way is to use a fixer
If you want to do it like that
What is the flow?
The flow is just one by one
The kind of hammering down
Break it
I don't understand what you're talking about
What kind of knot is it?
Like this kind of knot here
You can't see what's behind it
You just make a fake one
Just fix it here
But if it's like a scarf
It's better to pull it with a fixer
Wait for me to come down
Wow, there are so many people in the group
The team in our group is also growing
Do you have any other questions?
When will everyone have a holiday?
When is new year
No
I'll do it again
There will be
That
Videos
Last time it was a live stream, but the last time it was a live stream, it was to beat Jimmy, it was an activity that we did here, a dog wearing clothes, let's talk about it again, I don't have a dog's, I don't have a dog's, what is it, uh, material, that, OBJ.
You give it the normal size, if you want to grind its hair, it's better to delete it, and then add a shrink to it, the end, that's the gold, because you want it to be short in the gold,
and then you have to remember to find the head that's hidden in it, pull it out, when you pull it out, use the stick to fix it,
After that, look at the other side, if it's here, you can pull it down a little bit.
After that, delete the fixed one.
It's best to pull this strip out from the inside like this.
It's okay if it's not long enough.
Use the blue dot to see where this dot is.
For example, if it's here, you can pull it down a little bit.
When do you say you're going to upload this complete video?
If it's a complete video, it should be out tomorrow, right?
Because the subtitle is at the bottom.
It's also better to use the smaller one to import the model.
I don't understand.
Are you talking about the scarf?
Okay, after pulling it up here, just lift it up gently.
You have to make sure it's down here.
Don't pull it too tight.
After that, you can pull it up here, too.
Then we know that it must be overlapping in the middle, right?
Then you can add some fixed pins here.
After that, pull this end.
Like this.
Just pull it up like this.
Pull it over like this.
Then pull it over again.
Where did I put that fixed pin?
Let's take a look.
Pull it down.
Be careful when you pull it.
If you can't put it down like this,
you can pull this end.
Like this.
You have to be flexible in choosing which pin you want to pull.
For example, it's not easy to pull when the particle diameter is 20.
You can reduce the particle diameter during the process.
Reduce it to 15.
Let's put it this way.
It's best to import the model in a normal human proportion.
Because if you make the model smaller,
the particle diameter of the model will also be smaller in order not to penetrate.
So just import it in a normal proportion.
Then delete the points in the middle.
After deleting,
don't move these two fixed pins anymore.
Just pull it like this.
Put it here.
It will tighten by itself.
Then you must make sure.
Because I've been doing it for a long time,
I know what kind of state it is.
It won't penetrate.
If you're not sure,
you just open the hard drive.
You just keep the hard drive open.
This place is blue.
It's normal when it's green.
Let me demonstrate it to you.
Why do you often penetrate?
Because you pull this here and it's deformed.
You pull it red like this.
It will penetrate.
Do you understand?
So just don't pull it so tight.
And then in the process,
you must press the control key to simulate it at any time.
Then your scarf is done.
So actually making a scarf,
I think it doesn't really take long to make a scarf.
And then after you pull it,
you can change its length again.
I think I changed it too short.
After changing it,
you can change it back.
After changing it back,
is it 60 now?
Let's reduce its particle diameter a little bit.
If you think the triangle grid is not very good,
you can change it from this grid.
Because the scarf is usually a rectangle.
If you change it from this grid,
its array will also be a rectangle.
It will be more neat.
I usually use mm.
Because the unit I use
is the unit of mm that I usually use.
Is the input ratio mm or cm?
It depends on you.
What is the input ratio?
If you don't have a point when you input the default model,
you have to see if your model is a normal T-pose.
It's like...
Sorry.
I need to drink some water.
It's like I'm painting the top corner.
This pose is fine.
Unless your model's pose is really weird,
or you make it look like a T-pose,
or like an A-pose.
If it's an A-pose,
you might not be able to see it.
After you add the scarf,
let's see if the middle of the scarf
has a knot.
I'll add some pins.
I think its size
is OK.
Then I'll use my hand
to drag some wrinkles out.
Let's see its position.
For example, I want it to be softer,
so I'll put it like this.
After I'm done,
I can add some pins.
Double click.
I'll add pins along this edge.
After I'm done,
what is the input ratio?
We just used 60.
Let's add 80.
Oh my god.
I remember something.
80.
Then these wrinkles will come out.
Because you fixed
the pins on both sides.
Because you fixed the pins on both sides.
That means
the pins on both sides
won't spread out.
So if you change the input ratio again,
the pins will all be in the middle.
There will be more wrinkles.
Teacher,
what is the input ratio
of the back panel of your model?
Even if you change the pins to 1,
what is the input ratio?
What you're saying is...
I don't understand.
If you're posing,
there's no way you can set the position.
Yeah.
When you pose,
do you have the model
when you pose?
When you pose,
there must be a basic model.
If you already pose,
then it's a misunderstanding.
Otherwise,
you can let it return to the position
and put on the clothes
and then put on the model
oh yeah,
I don't understand
The model's back panel
doesn't correspond to the
particle panel,
but it's the hélicoids.
It's the air wall.
It doesn't mean that
if you lower the back panel,
the model's face will change.
It doesn't.
Oh,
I don't know, I think it should be
And then the scarf here
You just delete all the pins
And then simulate it
Let it go up a little bit
Because it's changed in size now
The amount here will change
Then it will tighten a little bit
After tightening
Just shape it
After shaping
The shape of the board will not change
You can understand
If you move it
It will return to where it was
Let me turn it
It will slowly
Come back again
This scarf is done
So it's actually very fast
It only took me a few minutes
To tie a scarf
If it's a pair of earrings
It might take longer
I can't show you
How to tie a pair of earrings
If it's a video
I won't be happy to show it
Do you have any other questions?
Before 9.15
I learned how to manipulate
What kind of manipulation did you learn?
Isn't this the manipulation
I just mentioned?
Was it because when I recorded the video
It was too fast
And then
I didn't record it
Oh oh oh oh
I heard my fan
Keep turning
The sound
How to make a stuffed animal
Stuffed animal
Add pressure
Just use two sheets
To sew it up and then add pressure
That's it
Add the right direction
Pressure
You have to sew it up
Then the right side out
Add the right pressure
The other side out
Add the negative pressure
You have to balance
I want to see what
Add it
Oh, I'll show you
I'll show you
My masterpiece
In Marvelous Designer
Make a ball
Yes, I'm already at the point of tightening
Will continue to stretch the plate
No, I won't teach you to show
I don't think I'll teach you to show
Because I can't do it myself
I'm in the Vray
Then adjust some lights
This is stupid
Like now
We have a plate
Then I give it
Clap the outer layer
Clap it
Be sure to open it in one second
Otherwise it will be confused
From the perspective of observation, you can see if this is facing the outside, right?
If it's facing the outside, you can add a positive pressure.
If it's facing the back, you can add a negative pressure.
If these two pressures are balanced, one is 5 and the other is negative 5,
and then you can start the simulation.
It's bulging!
It's okay.
No way, Arthur.
No way, no way.
There can't be any problem with this, right?
It cancelled the sound.
Oh, I remembered.
This is going to be a custom angle.
No way. It's impossible for it to turn over.
Why would anyone think that I would turn over?
It's impossible.
It's going to be very bulging.
And then it will form a ball.
Yes, my best skill is to make a weird-shaped ball out of fabric in Marvelous Designer.
It can roll, look.
Yuwen Hu, yes.
Yuwen Hu is also made from the Cologne version.
It's made from the Cologne version.
And then there's a positive pressure and a negative pressure.
Here's the question.
Quick question, quick answer.
If I turn it over, will I change its pressure?
If this version is turned over by me, that is, it's facing the front,
will its pressure be changed?
Quick question, quick answer.
If the first person answers correctly, send me a red envelope of 8.88 yuan.
I can only send 8.88 yuan.
Oh, you're too smart.
Free fly.
There's a Japanese word in between.
I don't know how to read it.
You're too smart.
I want it.
If you turn it over, your pressure will be changed to 5.
Then you can balance internally.
If this pressure is not 5, but negative 5, let's take a look.
It seems to be fine.
Why is this?
According to the rule, it should be flying.
Let's change the direction.
No, Asa.
It was supposed to fly.
Why isn't it flying now?
Oh, both of them are negative 5.
Sorry.
I'll give it a positive pressure.
I must see it take off.
Why can't it fly?
Forget it.
Anyway, it's...
You have to remember that if it's all facing the front,
you have to balance it.
No way.
Let me see.
Don't turn it over.
Turn it over again.
Why is it like this?
Oh, it's flying.
It's flying.
Brothers.
Did you see it?
No.
The reason why it's all facing the front is because...
This is not good.
For example, if one is facing the front and the other is facing the back,
you can't...
It won't take off.
Yes, it's very Q.
Oh, it's forgotten by you.
Where is it?
Okay, okay, okay.
It was like this just now.
Just now, it was because of the Cron layer.
It will automatically put its recognition line in the form of TURN.
TURN is equivalent to you being pressed.
Is there any problem with this?
I don't know what happened.
It will be flat.
It will be pressed down when the recognition line is pressed down.
It may not change after it is opened.
I'm tired.
I think I met a bug.
I think I met a bug for sure.
I have to open another version of AMD.
Wow.
I met a bug.
It turned over.
Forget it.
Let me show you the rolling egg yolk.
Let me show you how embarrassing it is.
Carrot bun.
Carrot bun is this.
If you add some internal lines, it will become a carrot bun.
Isn't it cute?
Isn't it bouncy?
Isn't it fun?
Why can I have an AMD?
My fan can make such a big sound.
It's okay to be right or wrong.
So you can use this method.
For example, you freeze it.
Sometimes you freeze it first, but as soon as it's cold, it will
freeze again.
The other way, you have to sugarcoat it a little.
It's a bit strong.
Right?
You can see a red hook button on the hook button, and the mother figure.
Oh boy.
There is something I have to create.
Let me show you how to create this.
拉链的锯齿条的大小,我看一下哦,拉链的锯齿条的大小,我看一下哦.
Sorry,那是因为这两个版片离开那个了。
发生了什么事?
薛老师,发生什么事了?
奇怪的问题又出现了。
你说的变响是什么变响?
诶,你把我难倒了,好像是不行的。
你好像只能就是,我给你看看哦。
哦?嗯?嗯?哦?哦?不行。
不行。
要准备吴操操的啊?
诶,你是不是要这样?
你是不是要这样?
条钮扣,为什么呢?
为什么是条钮扣啊?
是要这个是不是?
不要为难 everybody了,还是能为难一下的。
因为我刚开了固定比例了。
诶?
哦。
我刚好像是歪着加了呢。
好像是。
好像是!!
好像—.
It does look like it.
That means it works.
Yes.
It's just a sticker.
Oh, it's already 9.20.
What other questions do you have?
The function of the edge stickers.
Which one are you talking about?
Is it this function?
Can you add a 90 degree selection to 3D?
A lot of people are asking
what a 90 degree selection is.
Let me open the 3D window
and show you. Which one are you talking about?
Maorong hasn't appeared yet.
Maorong is going to show up in other apps!
Maorong can't appear in AMD.
Maorong is going to show up in other apps.
Blue or yellow width.
What is that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Because I know that
there's this function in CLO.
You can just
add an edge sticker.
But there's no such function in AMD.
A 90 degree selection?
I don't know.
Are you talking about
the 90 degree selection?
This one?
But I just asked her
and she said it's not this one.
But I just asked her and she said it's not this one.
Are you talking about this one?
No, it's not this one.
I don't have any other functions besides this one.
This is just a clothing measure.
It's gone.
I think you're talking about
the function in our brother's app.
Or are you talking about this one?
Oh, are you talking about this one?
Oh.
This is a sticky strip.
The function of this one
is similar to the one
in the waist belt
in our project file.
It prevents deformation.
It prevents deformation
because of stretching.
It's the same as the elastic
used in the collar.
It's just that
it has two pieces.
And the elastic
is just a string.
They're all used to prevent
deformation.
100% elastic is
is
just a string.
It's just a string.
In general,
if you look here,
for example,
let's pick a piece of clothing.
Let's pick a piece of clothing.
Let's pick a piece
that has deformation.
It's not that much of an
deformation.
Let's look at the waist belt.
You can see
the length of the waist belt is
157.
The length of the waist belt
is 123.
It means the length of the
collar.
The length of the waist belt
is because it has been stretched.
Let's say it's a model.
When she wears it on the model,
the skin of the model
is stretched.
If you look at the pressure,
it's going to be much stronger.
It's going to be much stronger.
Can you see
It's all red, which means that there is an obvious deformation on this side.
In order to prevent such deformation,
because the bottom plate is generally heavier,
and when it is sewn together with this plate, it is equivalent to dragging this plate down.
You want to prevent this plate from deforming,
and then you want it to maintain its original straight line state.
You have to apply 100% elasticity to it.
In this way, you can prevent some problems that are caused by the deformation,
which should be straight lines, but turn into curves.
Let me find out where the video is.
Look, before I apply 100% elasticity,
is this piece of clothing bent too much?
Then it will fall down again.
Like this one.
It is also bent here.
Then the middle part will also deform, and then it is narrow here.
If this is the case, you can add some elasticity to it.
After adding elasticity, does this line here suddenly become a straight line?
This is the 100% elasticity line.
Yes, it's okay to stick that strip.
But what about the strip?
90 degree rotation, red rotation.
Are you talking about this?
Or are you talking about this?
If you press the SHIFT key, there will be a subtraction.
Press the SHIFT key, and then rotate it,
there will be a subtraction.
If you press the SHIFT key, there will be a subtraction.
You see, I rotate it, rotate it, rotate it, rotate it,
and then it will suddenly stop.
That's the subtraction.
But you can't enter the exact number.
I feel that today's time is almost up.
We've been talking for almost two hours today.
If you have any questions,
you can ask them in our group.
That's it for today.
Let me see.
What's the difference between a straight line's elasticity
and a vertical line's elasticity?
A vertical line has no elasticity.
Only a straight line has elasticity.
Okay.
Okay, then see you next year.
Next year,
we're going to challenge what you can say.
aynı
이
For example, I added a name line, and there will be a custom obj here.
I forgot which one is custom obj.
Anyway, you can import this chain.
And then, you can create a name line by setting it to a thick line.
Although you call it a name line,
it's still a name line.
But we usually call it a name line.
Its Chinese translation is name line.
And then, if you add obj, you can do other name line effects.
And then, it's not a steel.
It's not a steel.
Yes, obj.
Directly to obj.
You can't go to Win2.
It has to be obj.
Therefore, if you see any problem, you can just write,
and we can edit and we can cut it to NewJae's code.
Yeah, that's it!
Is there any other problems?
Yes.
Then we will end it.
Any other questions?
Yes, no problem.
Thank you for watching today.
Thank you, guys.
Sh hysterics.
Thank you for coming to our live stream
The camera is here
If the video is transparent, you can only see this OBJ
Thank you for coming to our live stream
Thank you for your support of MAMALESS
I wish you a happy new year
Happy birthday
Health is the most important
And be happy every day
Happy New Year
Good luck
Oh, I forgot
What is the next award?
You can add us
Add us
I'll send you a huge red envelope of 8.88 yuan
Happy new year
Thank you for coming to our live stream
Thank you everyone
Goodbye everyone
Bye bye
Upload the video as soon as possible
Okay okay okay
I'll probably upload it tomorrow
If I don't upload it tomorrow, I might have to delay it until the end of the year
I guess
Upload it as soon as possible
Bye bye everyone
Happy new year
Bye bye
Thank you
Hi
It's okay
I'll upload the video tomorrow
Bye bye
Bye
See you tomorrow
Nope
Bye bye
Have a nice day
You're on your own
See you tomorrow
See you somewhere
Hello everyone
Colombia
Are you enjoying my
Journey to Panama. Are you happy?